I'm Peppa Pig. [snorts]
-This is my little brother, George.
-[snorts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[Mommy Pig snorts]
And this is Daddy Pig.
-[Daddy Pig snorts]
-[all laugh]
Peppa Pig. [snorts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is home time
at Peppa's playgroup.
[snorts] Daddy, Teddy Playgroup
is coming to stay.
-Who?
-Teddy Playgroup is our school mascot.
It's Peppa's turn to take him home.
He has pajamas, a photo album
and a toothbrush.
It's all in his suitcase.
I see.
[horn honks]
[narrator] Peppa, Daddy Pig
and Teddy Playgroup have arrived home.
Mommy Pig, we have a special guest
staying with us tonight.
Really? Who's that?
Teddy Playgroup.
He has pajamas, a photo album
and a toothbrush.
What is the photo album for?
We take photos of him
doing exciting things.
Oh.
My friends have took Teddy Playgroup
all over the world.
[Mommy Pig] London, Paris, Egypt...
Oh, I say, Teddy Playgroup
does have an exciting life.
Um, I hope he has an exciting time
with us.
[narrator] It is Peppa
and George's bedtime.
[Peppa & George giggling]
Everybody, this is Teddy Playgroup.
[in deep voice] Hello.
[in normal voice] He is our special guest.
You all have to make room.
Grr.
Oh. And that is Mr. Dinosaur.
He's not very good at talking.
Grr.
[Peppa & George giggle]
Let's take a photo
for Teddy Playgroup's album.
[snorts] Say cheese.
Cheese.
Daddy, Teddy Playgroup needs
to have an exciting time tomorrow.
Can we go to the North Pole?
Uh... how about the supermarket?
Yes! [snorts]
I don't think Teddy Playgroup
has ever been shopping before.
-[horn honks]
-[narrator] It is morning.
Peppa is taking Teddy Playgroup
to the supermarket.
[Peppa giggles]
This shop sells everything.
Oranges, apples, bananas.
[in deep voice] Very interesting.
[giggles]
[narrator] This is the checkout
where all the food is paid for.
[George giggles]
[narrator] George wants to take a picture.
-Okay, George.
-[snorts] Cheese.
[both] Cheese.
[laughs] That's enough pictures, George.
[George giggles]
Oh! Where is Teddy Playgroup?
[narrator] Teddy Playgroup is missing.
Daddy, you've lost Teddy Playgroup.
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'm sure we'll find him.
Hello. [snorts]
How was your day?
Daddy lost Teddy Playgroup.
Oh, no.
But I've got a plan to find him.
How are we going
to find Teddy Playgroup, Daddy?
First, we print out all the photos
we took of him.
[narrator] Mommy Pig
is unpacking the shopping.
Where are you going?
We're going to stick pictures
of Teddy Playgroup on trees.
Oh.
Daddy, wait for me.
Why are we sticking photos
on trees, Daddy?
[snorts] When people see the pictures
of Teddy Playgroup,
they'll know he's lost,
and they can help us find him.
[Peppa] Oh.
This is Teddy in my bed.
[Peppa giggles]
This is Teddy in the kitchen. [giggles]
And these are George's pictures
at the supermarket.
Oh! Teddy Playgroup. [snorts]
I know where he is.
[Peppa & George giggle]
Oh, hello.
Mommy, we know where Teddy Playgroup is.
Yes. He's in the shopping bag
with the pasta and tomatoes.
[all laughing]
[bell rings]
[narrator] Peppa is showing her class
Teddy Playgroup's photo album.
I was worried
that Teddy Playgroup wouldn't
have an exciting adventure with us.
Then, luckily, my Daddy lost him
at the supermarket.
-[students gasp]
-But we found him again in the shopping.
[students] Ooh.
That was an exciting adventure.
[in deep voice] Yes, it was.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Today is Danny Dog's birthday.
He is having a party.
[woofs] Yo-ho-ho!
[narrator] Everyone has come dressed
as pirates.
[children] Yo-ho-ho!
[narrator] Pedro Pony is dressed
as a cowboy.
Yeehaw!
[children giggle]
[woofs] Ahoy there, me hearties.
[narrator] It is Granddad Dog,
dressed as a pirate.
[snorts] Hello, Granddad Dog.
Call me Dog Beard.
[children] Hello, Dog Beard.
[woofs] Which of ye scurvy pirates
crave a ration
of swashbuckling o'er the briny seas?
Why is he talking funny?
[giggles] That's pirate's talk.
If you want to play my pirate game,
say "arr."
[children] Arr!
-Is it a dangerous game?
-No, Pedro.
Granddad Dog has promised me
it will be a very safe game.
[children] Aw.
But it will be exciting.
-So, who wants to play?
-[children] Arr!
Here be the plan.
Time was, I had a heap of gold
that was mine by right.
But I was hornswoggled by one Captain Hog.
What?
[narrator] Pirate talk is a bit difficult
to understand.
Captain Hog took my treasure.
[children] Ohh.
Know you
that Captain Hog is a fearsome pirate.
Some of you may already know him
as Grandpa Pig.
[children] Ah. Grandpa Pig.
[all giggle]
The game is to go to Captain Hog's hideout
and get back my treasure
without being caught.
[all] Hooray!
[narrator] Everyone is excited
to be playing the pirate game.
[dialing]
[line rings]
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
We're on our way.
Jolly good.
[narrator] Grandpa Pig and Polly Parrot
are guarding the pirate treasure.
Be the Black Galleon fast
and the wind at our backs we'll away.
What does that mean?
Run to the boat.
[children] Yo-ho-ho!
Yeehaw!
[children giggle]
Whoa, there.
Put your life jackets on.
[narrator] On Granddad Dog's boat,
all the children must wear life jackets.
That scurvy Dog Beard should
be here by now. [snorts]
Here's a nice cup of tea, Grandpa Pig.
Oh, thank you, Granny Pig.
At last.
Are we all ready now?
Mr. Dog Beard, I need to go to the toilet.
-And me.
And me.
What can be keeping them?
[dialing]
Hello, Granddad Dog?
I thought you said you were on your way.
Yes, yes, we're almost there.
It's taken a while
to get my crew together.
Anchors away.
Full sail.
[children] Aye, aye, Dog Beard.
[children giggles]
♪ Oh, jolly pirates, we ♪
♪ That sail the deep blue sea ♪
♪ To find our golden treasure ♪
♪ Full sail, ahoy, yippee! ♪
Land ahoy.
[narrator] The children have arrived
at Grandpa Pig's orchard.
[children giggle]
The game is to get that treasure
without being caught.
[mothers] Hooray for the pirates.
Shush, Mommy.
I hope there are no pirates around here,
trying to take my lovely treasure.
[narrator] Peppa and her friends
have got the coins without being caught.
It's chocolate coins.
[narrator] Everybody loves
chocolate coins.
[all] Yum, yum, yum.
Ah.
-Got you.
-[narrator] Granddad Dog has been caught.
Try and take my treasure, would you?
'Tis mine.
I won it fair and square.
Oh, no, you didn't.
Oh, yes, I did.
[barking and snorting]
[clears throat] Thank you,
Captain Hog and Dog Beard,
-for the lovely pirate game.
-Oh, you're very welcome.
Uh, oh, yes.
It's been lots of fun.
[children] Happy Birthday, Danny.
This be the best pirate party ever!
[all] Arr!
[all laughing]
[Peppa reading on-screen text]
[Mr. Potato] Up, down, up, down...
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are watching Mr. Potato on television.
[snorts] I love watching programs
about keeping fit.
Up, down.
Now, here are some lovely drawings
I've been sent.
This is an apple.
[Peppa & George] Ooh.
Remember, eating fruit
and vegetables helps you stay fit.
I'm good at eating fruits and vegetables.
And exercise is important.
Today you can see me open
a new sports center in town.
Mommy, can we go and see Mr. Potato?
It's a long way to go
to see a potato, Peppa.
He's not any old potato.
[snorts] This is Mr. Potato.
Can we go and see him, Mommy, please?
-Oh, all right.
-[Daddy Pig & children] Hooray!
[all laugh]
[narrator] Everyone has come to see
Mr. Potato open the new sports center.
[horn honking]
Look. It's Mr. Potato.
[crowd] Mr. Potato!
-[horn honks]
-Oh, it's just Peppa.
[crowd] Oh.
Hello, everyone.
[crowd] Hello, Peppa.
Suzy thought you were Mr. Potato.
[snorts] I don't look like Mr. Potato.
No, you're much too big.
Mr. Potato is bigger than me.
No, he's not.
He's a potato.
And potatoes are this big.
[horn honking]
[woofs] There's Mr. Potato.
[narrator] Mr. Potato has come to town.
Please, welcome your friend
and mine, Mr. Potato.
[crowd] Hooray!
Wow, that's a big potato.
I declare this sports center open.
Fantastic.
We must all exercise
and eat fruit and vegetables.
Which ones should we eat, Mr. Potato?
Apples, oranges, carrots, tomatoes.
-Potatoes?
-Um...
Why aren't you small,
like a normal potato?
-Uh...
-Because he's not a normal potato.
He's got legs.
Normal potatoes don't have legs.
He's a super potato.
[snorts] We watch your show every morning.
Very good.
And remember to send me your drawings.
[children] We will.
[children giggle]
[bell rings]
[narrator] Peppa and her friends
are at playgroup.
Children, today we will do drawings
for Mr. Potato.
[children] Hooray!
[woofs] I'm drawing a pineapple.
I'm drawing a carrot.
Very good.
-What are you drawing, Emily?
-A pea.
Lovely. And Pedro?
It's a super potato.
Oh, I see.
And George has drawn a wonderful tomato.
[snorts, then giggles]
Peppa, what vegetable have you drawn?
[snorts] My Daddy watching television.
[Madame Gazelle] Oh, excellent.
Now, we put the drawings in an envelope
and post them to Mr. Potato.
[rooster crows]
[narrator] It is morning
and time for the Mr. Potato show.
Please, welcome your friend
and mine, Mr. Potato.
We posted some drawings
to Mr. Potato in an envelope.
Did you get the envelope?
He can't hear you, Daddy.
He's on television.
Oh, yes, of course.
I've received
an envelope full of drawings.
-This tomato looks very juicy.
-That's George's picture.
[George snorts, then giggles]
Well done, George.
But this picture
from Peppa Pig is my favorite.
Wow! That's my picture.
It shows Daddy Pig watching TV.
Hmm.
Looks like Daddy Pig needs some exercise.
-Eh? What?
-Come on, Daddy Pig.
Let's do some jumping up and down.
Oh, all right.
[Mr. Potato] Up, down, up, down.
[narrator] Daddy Pig
likes jumping up and down.
[Mr. Potato] Up, down, up, down.
[narrator] Everyone likes jumping
up and down.
[children giggling]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Today Peppa and her friends
are going on a train ride.
[Mr. Rabbit blows whistle]
[narrator] Mr. Rabbit
is the stationmaster.
How many tickets?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ten child tickets
and one teacher ticket, please.
Now, children, do not lose these tickets.
[blows whistle]
Can I see your tickets, please?
[Pedro] Uh...
I've lost my ticket.
Oh, dear, Pedro, you must be more careful.
There's your ticket.
[giggles]
[chuckles] Try not to lose it again.
-[whistle toots]
-Here comes the train.
[whistle tooting]
Choo choo.
[narrator] Miss Rabbit
is the train driver.
All aboard.
[children] Hooray!
[blows whistle]
[whistle tooting]
♪ Clickety clack, clickety clack
The train rides on the track ♪
♪ Huff and puff, huff and puff
Clickety clickety clack ♪
[children giggle]
Ah-ho. Here are your activity sheets.
[children] Ooh.
[narrator] The children have to spot
everything that is on the activity sheet.
A boat.
A signal box.
[woofs] And a tunnel.
[snorts] I can see trees.
-Are trees on the list?
-Uh, no.
I can see clouds.
-[Danny] Are clouds on the list?
-No.
I can see Granddad Dog.
-Ahoy there.
-[all] Hello, Granddad Dog.
[horn toots]
[whistle toots]
Is Granddad Dog on the list?
Silly Peppa.
My Granddad won't be on the list.
But he is sailing a boat.
And a boat is on the list.
[children] Hooray!
[narrator] The children tick the boat
on their activity sheets.
[blows whistle]
Tickets, please.
[narrator] Mr. Rabbit has come
to check everyone's ticket.
Uh... I think I've lost my ticket.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
[meows] There's your ticket, Pedro.
-You were sitting on it.
-[giggles]
Now, you try not to lose it again, Pedro.
[narrator] The train is going
slowly uphill.
[children] Whee!
[narrator] The train is going
quickly downhill.
[children giggling]
Madame Gazelle, I feel a bit sick.
Can I go to the front, please?
Okay, Pedro.
You can go to the front of the train.
[Pedro giggles]
♪ Doo da dum dum, da dee da ♪
-[neighs]
-Hello, Pedro.
Not feeling very well? Would you
like to drive the train for a bit?
Yes, please.
[Pedro giggling]
[whistle toots]
♪ Clickety clack, clickety clack
The train rides on the track ♪
♪ Huff and puff, huff and puff
[whistle toots]
[children giggling]
[bell clanging]
[snorts] A signal box. That's on our list.
[children] Hooray!
[narrator] The children tick
the signal box on their activity sheets.
The signal has stopped the train
so that someone important can cross.
[quacking]
It's Mrs. Duck and her friends.
[all quacking]
Oh, we still haven't seen a tunnel.
[all gasp]
[Peppa] Oh, it's gone dark.
-[Suzy] We're in a tunnel.
-[all giggle]
[narrator] The tunnel is the last thing
on the activity sheet.
[all] Hooray! [giggle]
Last stop.
All change.
Everybody off now.
But, Madame Gazelle,
how are we going to get home?
[chuckles] Peppa, we are back
where we started.
[narrator] The train has gone
in a big circle.
[blows whistle] Tickets, please.
[children giggle]
Um...
Pedro's lost his ticket again.
-Um...
-Pedro.
Can I have my hat back, please?
[children] There's Pedro's ticket.
Oh, that's where I put it.
[all laughing]
♪ Clickety clack, clickety clack
The train rides on the track ♪
♪ Huff and puff, huff and puff
Clickety clickety clack ♪
♪ Clickety clack, clickety clack
The train rides on the track ♪
♪ Huff and puff, huff and puff
[whistle toots]